GUNNAR HARRISON (he/him) is a multidisciplinary graphic designer based in Salt Lake City, Utah. His practice incorporates Identity Design, Motion Graphics, Image Making, UI/UX Design, Type Design, and Front-End Development. He has worked with a range of clients including: Nike, A24 Films, Google, Nécessaire, Otis College of Art and Design, ArtBook, Actual Source Books, and others.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**Actual Source** 

Provo, UT

Senior Graphic Designer Feb 2020 – Present Graphic Designer Apr 2018 – Jan 2020 Graphic Design Intern Jan 2018 – Apr 2018

214 Co.

New York, NY

Graphic Design Intern May 2017 – Aug 2017

Wallaroo Media

Provo, UT

Graphic Designer May 2015 – May 2017

**EDUCATION** 

**Brigham Young University** 

BFA Graphic Design Jun 2014 – Apr 2018

## **SKILLS**

Adobe CC (Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, AfterEffects, Media Encoder, XD), Figma, Cinema 4D, Glyphs, Git, HTML, CSS, jQuery

## **AWARDS**

ADC Young One Silver Cube	2018
Graphis New Talent Gold	2018
Graphis New Talent Silver	2018
Bryan Peterson Scholarship	2017
McCray Magleby Scholarship	2017
Talent Award Scholarship	2016

## **FEATURES**

Mouthwash	Web, 2020
The Brand Identity	Web, 2020
New Aesthetic 1	<b>Print</b> , 2019
BYUCFAC	Web, 2018
Klikkenthéke	Web, 2018
Extra Point	<b>Print</b> , 2018
DesignArts Utah	Exhibition, 2017

WEBSITE gunnaris.me

EMAIL hello@gunnaris.me